Guide to the Undergraduate Affairs, Yale College, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the Dean of Student Affairs, Yale College, 1961-2011; 2000-2011; Accession 2016-A-079
  - Freshman Handbook Class of '14, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Map Class of '14, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Calendar of Opening Days (COD) Class of '14, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Son Daughter July Mailing Class of '14, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - July Mailing Class of '14, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - May Mailing Class of '15, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 7)